And how was your timetable?
你的课程安排怎么样？
Was it a very busy year?
是很忙碌的一年吗？
Very,very busy.They make you work very hard.
非常忙碌，他们要让你非常努力的学习。
Apart from lectures,we had practical sessions in a lot of subjects.
除了讲座，我们的很多科目都有实习课。
We did these in small groups.
我们在小组里完成这些。
I had to go and work four hours every week in a community pharmacy.
我不得不每周在社区药房工作4小时。
Actually,I enjoyed this very much - meeting new people all the time.
事实上我很享受这一切，总是能遇见新的人。
Then in second semester,we had to get experience in hospital dispensaries,
之后在第二学期，我们就去了医院的药房实习，
so every second day we went to one of the big hospitals and worked there.
所以每两天我们就去其中一家大医院并在那里工作。
And on top of all that we had our assignments,which took me a lot of time.
而且最重要的是我们还有作业，这花了我很多时间。
Oh,I nearly forgot,between first and second semesters,we had to work full-time for two weeks in a hospital.
我差点忘了，在第一和第二学期之间，我们不得不在医院全职工作两周。
That does sound a very heavy year.
听起来是任务很重的一年。
So are you pleased now that you did it?
那么你喜欢你的工作吗？
Do you feel some sense of achievement?
你感到有成就感吗？
Yeah,I do feel much more confident,which I suppose is the most important thing.
是的，我确实感到更有自信了，我想这也是最重要的。
And have you got any recommendations for people who are studying from overseas?
你对海外求学的学生有什么建议吗？
Well,I suppose they need very good English.
我想他们需要英语很好。
It would be much better if they spent more time learning English before they enter the university,
最好是他们能在入学前多花时间学好英语，。
because you can be in big trouble if you don't understand what people are saying and you haven't got time to translate.
因为如果你听不懂人们说话又没时间翻译的话，你会陷入大麻烦
Anything else? Well,as I said before,the biggert problem for me was a lack of familiarity with the education system here.
还有吗？正如我之前说的，对于我来说，最大的问题是缺乏对这里教育体系的认知。
It sounds as if it was a real challenge.Congratulations,Kira. Thanks,Paul.
这听起来像是一个真正的挑战。祝贺你，基拉。-谢谢，保罗。